Swetank Subham

Senior Software Engineer, Python

hone +91 9110 09 0019

Email swetanksubham.r@gmail.com

LinkedIn /in/swetank-subham/

Website https://swetanksubham.com/

Address Muzaffarpur, Bihar



With around **3 years** of experience in Software **Back-end Development** and **Management**, which includes several web-apps, scripts, APIs. I describe myself as a life-long learner, implementer and tech enthusiast. I prefer smart work but always ready for hard work if required.

Skills

Python	Shell Scripting		JavaScript	Pandas	Git	Jira	Li	nux	Docker	Dat	a Structures
HTML	CSS	ООР	Tesseract	Agile Methodology			HP	MySQL Or		penCV	PySpark
RASA	Sanic JSON		N Django								

Work History

Knowlarity Communications Pvt. Ltd., Gurgaon **Software Developer**

30th September 2021 – 29th May 2022 [8 months]

Worked on OBD (Outbound Calls). Role includes feature development, enhancement and possible optimisations, troubleshooting production issues, code review, daily stand-up and assistance during production activities.

Great Software Laboratory Pvt. Ltd., Pune

2nd July 2019 – 29th September 2021 [2 year 3 months]

Software Engineer

Worked on multiple projects. Role includes architecture design for new projects, feature development, enhancement and possible optimisations, troubleshooting production issues, code review, daily stand-up and assistance during production activities.

Great Software Laboratory Pvt. Ltd., Pune

2nd August 2018 - 30th June 2019 [11 months]

Software Engineer (Intern)

Worked as a full-stack developer. Role includes feature development. Enhancement and possible optimisations, daily stand-up.

Education

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science and Engineering

2015 - 2019

Lovely Professional University, Punjab

Certifications

Data Structures and Algorithms, Nano Degree, Udacity

ID: CANUTXDS

Link: https://graduation.udacity.com/confirm/CANUTXDS

The Complete 2022 Web Development Course - Build 15 Projects, Udemy

ID: UC-30HPQA6I

Link: https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-30HPQA6I/